Dmitriy Aloyts

Email: dmitriy@iinet.net.au | Phone: 0425353737 | Clarinda, Victoria <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>GitHub</u> | <u>Website</u>

Full Stack Web Developer leveraging a background in software development. Self-motivated and driven problem-solver, passionate about clean and structured coding with great attention to details. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Development from the Monash University of Melbourne.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, AJAX, The Command Line, Object-Oriented Programming, Experience in all stages of SDLC - from system analysis through to design, coding and testing.

PROJECTS

Music Application | JavaScript, HTML, CSS | GitHub| Live Lead Developer
The data application retrieves information about a song or a singer from APIs.

- Led team of 4 and research data input and output from APIs.
- Used Bulma package for CSS formatting and jQuery for logic.

Password Generator | JavaScript, HTML, CSS | <u>GitHub</u>| <u>Live</u> **Sole Developer** *The application generates a random password.*

- Developed UI to generate a password based on user user-selected criteria.
- Client side app with dynamically updated HTML/CSS powered by JavaScript.

Inner Peace Project | React, JavaScript, MongoDB, | <u>GitHub</u>| <u>Live</u> Sole Developer The application generates a random password.

- Developed Front End using React.js to generate new blogs and add comments.
- The MERN app dynamically updates MongoDB and is hosted on Heroku.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Computershare Technology Services

February 2000 - May 2012

Software Developer

Melbourne, VIC

Developed creative solutions for listed on ASX companies while maintaining development methodologies and processes. Upgraded core system processes to allow users to have more flexibility and control over the system. Trained new developers while working on maintenance of the system.

Key Accomplishments:

- Led a group of 3 developers on AMP Data Warehouse project.
- Was awarded with 2 AFL tickets for successfully completing ANZ Proxy Meeting project.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lotus Doors February 2018 - Present

Joiner

- Efficiently multitasked across production lines.
- Effectively worked in a team of 10 people.

BMM testlabs March 2016 – February 2018

Software tester

- Assessed technology integrity, accountability and functionality.
- Successfully reviewed source code.

DHL Express May 2012 – March 2016

Courier Driver

• Effectively performed tasks in a very fast-pased environment.

EDUCATION

Monash University, Melbourne 2020

Monash Coding Boot Camp - Certificate in Full Stack Web Development.

Interim Technology Training Institute, Melbourne

1999 Diploma of Business Programming.